What are your thoughts on invoicing?
A full year upfront so they can go get a loan for marketing,
they don't want to pay up front.
We raise a premium on month to month going down that path.
I don't love it personally.
Like number one, if they have to take a loan up,
that means they can't afford it, number one.
Number two, they still have to pay it plus a premium on it
for the loan amount, you know,
and you're also paying for the,
that doesn't really make sense actually.
If it was for a three month contract, right?
And they took out a loan to pay for a three month project,
like if they needed a new website for example, right?
And they were like, yeah, we can't afford it right now,
but we know that we'll be able to do in the future.
They take out a loan, they pay
the bank back over a year or two.
That makes sense. But taking a loan out
for a full year contract doesn't really make sense
because it's already amortized.
If you think about it. You know,
it's like if they're gonna pay you month to month
and they'll just pay you month to month
and asking somebody to pay for a year
of marketing upfront is a lot of money,
you're talking about a hundred grand or more.
So that to me doesn't really,
doesn't really make too much sense.
You know? So if you were gonna say consigning year contract
with us for a thousand dollars a month,
or if you prefer to pay month, a month,
then it's $1,200 a month.
That would make sense. 'cause then you know, you're,
you're incentivizing them to lock into a contract
and you're that, that would make sense.
But having them finance a year upfront
and having you pay them,
pay you a year front doesn't really have any value them
because they're just gonna be paying the same,
they're gonna be paying monthly then to a bank,
the same amount plus whatever the loan expenses on top of
that, if that makes sense.
Thoughts on therapy services,
being able to afford the service.
That's been my niche and I've been charging about 1500
or $2,000 monthly.
Like this service, my service,
technically we're probably doing the same thing.
We're doing marketing, SEO advertising, whatever it is,
we're just doing it to different clients, right?
And that price point is determined by a couple of things.
Number one is determined by what are your costs
to deliver the what are our, my costs
and your costs to deliver the service.
And doing it for personal injury lawyers means a lot
of content, a lot of links.
We have to, we generate reviews which call, like we do a lot
of stuff, which means it's,
'cause it's very, very competitive
to do personal injury marketing versus therapy.
Not uncompetitive, but not nearly
as competitive as personal injury, right?
So your costs on that are gonna be lower, right?
So just inherently there's gonna be discrepancy between
you seeing a quote for a personal injury firm
and a therapy service, right?
That's number one. Number two though,
and this is why we're really able to charge a premium, is
because of the volume
and the return in terms of how much the customer is worth
to them worth to them versus a customer being
worth to a therapist, right?
I don't have the data on therapy.
I would imagine that most people churn off a therapist
pretty quick and maybe only go once or twice.
So like, I don't know what the average client value is
to a therapy, right?
Especially if they're on insurance
or pay as you go, whatever that looks like.
Personal injury law, we're talking, some
of these guys are making a million dollars per client,
that's not the, but the minimum
that they're making is like $25,000 per client.
So because of that, if I'm charging $10,000 a month,
I know I only need to get them one
or two clients per month to make it at least a net ROI.
And if they hit one, then they're gonna be paying
for five years of our services.
Right now with therapy, there might be a cap.
There's definitely a cap on
how much a client is worth to them.
So it's gonna dramatically impact your pricing too.
So that's really the thing with these niches
and selecting niches, it's one,
what is my internal cost to deliver this?
And like the market expectation of what it costs
and two, how much can they make off of it?
That's really the thing where you can start getting into
pricing and economies of scale and charging more
because they're making so much off what we do.
If we do it well, they're comfortable paying it.
And that's kind of what they're getting quoted at too,
because that one of the market knows it.
So that, that's part one of this.
Part two of this is
what is something like you're getting pushed back a lot.
I talk to Sean a lot about this a lot in the inner circle,
which is he works with dentists
and there's definitely a cap just in terms
of what you can charge for that.
And there's, but it's also
because of the expectation of what they've,
what they've been paying
or what they've been accustomed to paying for that service.
And I would imagine that there's a
lot of that also going on in therapy.
So if you're charging 1500 to 2000,
because that's what you, that's all you can charge, right?
When, when I talked to Sean, you know, he's like, I,
they just aren't comfortable paying more than 2000, 2,500,
$3,000 all inclusive marketing services.
So what you've gotta be able to do,
and this is why this program is so valuable for you,
is saying, okay, I like working with therapists
because I believe in it, or I'm an ex therapist
or you know, if you wanna stick with that vertical
and that niche and also 'cause you have a brand there,
then you, you might be able to say, okay, like I just,
the market caps me too.
Like they might make a million dollars off of this,
but I'm just capped at what I can charge them
because of everyone else that's quoting them
because of, you just said their l lt
for a th therapy client is three to 5,000, right?
So you're capped at, call it 1500, $2,000 per month.
That's okay. What you have to be able to do is you have
to be able to build a process that's so tight
and so efficient that you can lower your cost
to deliver the service.
So for us, for example,
I'm quoting this big personal injury firm right now,
and it's gonna be $20,000 a month.
We're not making that much more profit off of that
because we have to build so much content, we have
to do digital pr, you know,
we're getting them on like Forbes, places that
that costs thousands of dollars.
So we have to do a lot more work.
So we have to charge more work for it,
but we're not necessarily making
that much more profit than we'd be doing off of like a six
to $7,000 a month SEO client personal injury.
So for you though, that means saying,
how can I reduce my costs?
So how can I drop my costs on content,
on delivering our service on whatever that looks like
to make more profit on that $2,000 per month.
That, that, that becomes the goal of saying, okay,
if I can't raise my prices, how do I reduce my,
my operating costs or
how much the service costs me to deliver it?
Okay. What do you think
of running Facebook retargeting ads for agency owners?
B2B, lead gen Facebook retargeting is kind of a, it's kind
of a, it's kind of a kind of a dated topic.
We really don't run much remarketing on Facebook
because it doesn't really work like that anymore per se,
because of the way that Facebook has,
because of the way that Facebook has
just changed their targeting.
So for example, when I first started running Facebook ads,
we used to be able to upload like URLs.
I mean I guess you still can, but it just isn't working.
Where you be able to upload audience
custom audiences that would actually work.
Now Facebook is based, like, if you didn't build
that audience inside of Facebook, then
we can't really match it.
One, because we're under so much the cookie is dead
and we're under so much fire with data privacy that like
you have to basically build the audience
inside of Facebook ads.
In other words, if you're going to run retargeting ads,
you have to run ads to build, build retargeting lists that
that makes sense, which costs money.
Agencies, trust me,
don't really like spending a lot of money.
Y'all are, we are stingy folks, trust me.
So, you know, it's not as simple as coming in
and just being like, Hey, we'll set up retargeting ads
forever, who comes to your website?
Because one people who, most people go to my website,
it's you all, it's not lawyers.
You know, like most people that go
to agency websites are not customers, they're just not.
And second of all, if they wanted to work
with you the first time they went, they probably would've,
you know, they probably would've booked something.
It's like there's this common misconception around
remarketing where people are like,
oh my God, you're totally right.
I was on your website, I read an article, it was really good
and the funniest thing, I just forgot to book a call.
So I'm so glad that you re-serve
that ad now while I'm scrolling in line at Chipotle for me
to then go in and book a call
and fill out, you know what I'm saying?
Like it doesn't really, the concept
of remarketing is not marketers square that.
It's like, it's that simple, but it doesn't work like that
to really do remarketing, right?
It's not actually remarketing,
it's just increased visibility.
Like the reason why our ads work is because I sit with Yon
and I tell him, I don't wanna see my the same
ad more than once.
I want to see different selfie videos,
images, I wanna see me in the studio.
And that's what I hear when I talk
to prospects when they're like,
yeah dude, you're all of my feed.
And it's not because I want to, it's
because I'm all over their feeds.
Because they keep on getting more and more and more ads.
So the point I guess that I'm making is that like,
it sounds like I'm, I'm just assuming this,
it sounds like you're trying to set up like a low cost,
easy Facebook ads offer,
but Facebook ads just doesn't work like that.
Like there's, there's very few businesses right now in the
world that you could walk into set up remarketing
ads ad to make money for it.
Maybe some e-commerce businesses
that are doing like a tremendous amount of volume.
But for agencies, no, they don't have any,
like most agencies barely have a website built out.
They're not doing anything on social media.
They don't have creative, they're doing no marketing.
So that would just be my sense that, like I do think
that doing Facebook ads for agencies is a good offer,
but it's not as simple as just coming in
and setting up remarketing ads.
You're gonna have to do the exact same thing that you do
for everyone, which is creative strategy, video development,
scripting, media buying, like it's a, it's a lot
of work in my experience with agencies, just
to be quite frank there,
there's a reason why we don't have a done for you offer
for agencies and just, and this is no shade,
but like agencies don't wanna spend money.
They just don't. They're like, there's a lot of costs
that go into running it in terms of like software
and people that when it comes
to investing in their own marketing
And advertising, it's a really hard sell.
It's a really, really, really hard sell to get an agency
to dig in and be like, Hey, you're gonna pay us 2,500 a
month for Facebook ads management if that's
what you're charging hypothetically, you're also gonna have
to get on video and make and put in time and effort
and then you're gonna have to spend at least another
$5,000 a month.
So you're, we're talking about like an $8,000 investment per
month plus a lot of extra effort.
We were not, it was an offer
that we like dipped our toe in the water
and we're like, no, we're not doing this.
So why we teach it instead?
Because agencies are are awesome because y'all wanna learn.
Y'all are willing to learn. You show up, you put in the time
and effort to figure it out yourself,
but they're very, very hesitant to pay for it
unless it's like super cheap.
And if they're gonna pay you super cheap,
then you're not gonna be able to build the right,
the right people to help deliver it
because it's quite a bit of work to do Facebook ads, right?
Trust me, I know because we do it for our clients
and we have a team of like six, seven people now
that it's a lot of work to do it for our clients.
But I do fully believe that Facebook ads are
by far in a way, the best way to get leads
and clients to why you see me everywhere doing it.
They just work. So if you can figure it out in there,
you can keep asking questions about it.
I can take a look at it for you
and on these calls and, and help you out.
But that one I would say it's gonna have
to be more than just retargeting ads.
That would be my advice. What strategy would you recommend
for a client who verbals sets, deck steps
and then ghosts won't answer calls, texts, emails,
and receptionist stonewall as well.
I also understand buyers are liars.
We provide SEO Facebook, uh, Google for law firms.
It's just part of the business auto unfortunately for us.
Like I get ghosted a lot too, you know,
I would say like at least 30% of like,
I get them all the way to the finish line through
that whole process and 30% of people still ghost me.
The reason being is, you know, you have to ask yourself too,
like, have you ghosted a a vendor before
and why did you ghost them?
Right? For me it's usually kind of like a I'm interested
but just not right now type thing.
That's just my, that's my opinion on what happens a lot.
I just think you need to give 'em some space personally.
Like if you've, if they're completely stonewall you,
it means I'm not interested right now.
And you just continuing to push is probably only gonna annoy
the crap outta 'em and burn a future relationship with them.
So I would say set it up, set a marker in your calendar,
in your CRM for 90 days and follow up every 90 days.
You know? And, and what I'd like to do is instead
of saying like, Hey, I'm following up
on the proposal that I sent.
I like to say something like, Hey, we, you know,
we just got a, like here's a, a link to a new,
a new case study that we just published about a law firm
just like yours where we're getting them, you know,
clients at a thousand dollars each when you kind
of like refresh their memory from the top to be like, oh,
this is why I was interested in the first place.
Because, because they're gonna forget about the proposal.
You're probably also not wanting the,
the scope maybe expires or changes over time,
but it's annoying man.
It's part of the business lawyers that are especially like,
it's ironic, these, these people are like, they swear
that their, their time is the
most valuable thing on the planet.
'cause that's how they charge. And then like they ask you
for all this stuff, like they reach out to you
and they're like, oh my God, I'm super interested.
And then it's like, but you don't have 30 seconds
to be like, to just answer an email or text message.
It's crazy. Why do you choose to sell blended search
SSEO and Google and meta ads separately versus
multi-channel bundled just
because of the, the cost for us to do all of them together.
For most of these clients,
they're looking at like a hundred grand a month in,
in ad costs, right?
We work with a lot of personal injury firms.
You're look, I mean the a hundred grand is probably
having probably 50 grand a month right?
To, for starting point, because you gotta spend 20 on
Facebook, you gotta spend 30 on Google,
and then SEO retainer is gonna be another 10.
Our ad buying costs are gonna be like another six.
So you're looking at 16.
Yeah, you're looking at like 65, $70,000.
So that's why we don't even the biggest law firms, you know,
we work with some very, very, very large law firms.
And what we find too is they actually like
to keep separate vendors who are specialists and things,
but we just like to get our foot in the door with stuff,
do a good job, and then try and like cross sell from there.
We find it more effective.
But if you're doing it with, again,
you just have to know your industry.
For dentists, they might be like, well we don't wanna,
like I don't have an internal marketing person.
I don't wanna work with five different vendors.
If you can do it all, do it all,
you know, that's what I would say.
It just for us, it's, it's a different market.
It's a different industry. Um,
and it, it just drastically changes things.
You normally handle all the sales processes yourself.
Do you have a sales team or person?
And if so, at what point did you
decide to get a sales team person?
Awesome question. So I've gone back
and forth for quite some time on this in terms
of people and hiring.
And I used to have a dedicated sales rep
who would take all the calls, you know,
work on the proposals, it just didn't work out.
I went through two or three different salespeople in
that like traditional sales role
and it just didn't work out.
The reason being, and I see this now too,
I'm currently using being white labeled
by a very large agency and they have sales reps,
but they don't get the service like they still need me
and they need their service delivery team.
Like they, they're, when they sell, I watched them sell,
you know, like PPC ads to, to law firms.
The salespeople can't sell it.
They don't know what the f they're talking about.
They're like relationship people.
They send 'em to conferences, you know, they,
they're like almost account people, you know,
but they can talk at a high level.
But whenever the strategy
or the proposal needs to come on,
they pull in people from their service delivery team.
So like I, and I'm like, yo, you're asking like,
are you paying your director of paid search to come in
and sit on resales calls a week?
'cause like this is a lot of work.
And then he goes back to hammering the campaigns after that.
To me, I would never ask that of my people.
I'll pull like Caesar onto calls or Francisco onto calls,
but I'll pull 'em on for like a 30 minute call
and be like, Hey, this is the guy
you're gonna be working with.
I just wanna introduce you and,
and help you build a relationship.
Like that's, I'm not asking to
do proposals and like pitch and sell.
Like they're just there to shake hands, you know?
So I went through a salesperson who, you know,
had a couple salespeople who had SEO experience,
but even that, like, we were just losing too many deals
because what was happening was is
that in the agency sales space, you need
to be part salesperson in terms of understanding how
to sell, but more importantly, you need to be a consultant.
Meaning you need to understand the nature of
what it is we're selling real quick so it doesn't die on us.
And that is really, really hard
to find in terms of a people person.
Usually those people are running their own business, right?
Because if you're gonna try and find somebody who can sell,
but also do very advanced SEO work, it's, it's a,
it's a very hard person to try and find.
If you can find that person and you have enough deals to,
to make them enough money, go for it.
So what I was finding was that I was either stuck
with a person who was like good at sales,
but bad at analysis, which to me is worse than a person
who is good at analysis, but bad at sales because,
but either way, we were just losing deals.
So I decided to kind of go back to the drawing board
and say, all right,
sales is a full-time position for somebody.
It can't be me 'cause I have too much going on.
Because when we're talking about like marketing sales,
when we're talking about like proposals,
I mean you've seen the analysis we put together.
It's a lot of work. So it's, it, it takes hours to to
to put together a proposal
and analysis management, CRM, emails, all that stuff,
plus the calls, you know, all that type of stuff.
So what I did is I went out
and I said, alright, where are the bottlenecks
for me personally, I'm on Zoom calls all day.
I don't mind being on Zoom calls.
It doesn't really take a lot of my
bandwidth, my mental energy.
I can do this all day so I can handle the calls.
Plus I'm really good on them.
You know, like, nobody sells this better than me.
Nobody talks about this better than me.
And you know, I'm able to build a really fast
and good relationship with prospects very quickly
when I'm on the calls with them.
So I said, I'll handle that, but what I can't handle
and what I don't wanna handle is
everything that happens after the call.
So I went out and I hired somebody.
She was working at an agency.
She is in Estonia,
I believe her name's Annette, she's awesome.
She's an SEO specialist.
She's been doing legal SEO for years.
She knows SEO very, very well.
I went out and I hired her
and I pay her a base salary, a base monthly salary,
and then I give her like a 2%
or 1% commission on any deal that closes
that she worked on with me.
'cause there's some deals that I'll, like the Facebook ads
stuff she doesn't get involved with because it's, it's,
it's just a templated deck that I send them.
But for SEO she does that analysis.
She puts together the scope of work.
She manages a CRM, she does a, she does a lot of work.
And that has really opened up our sales process
because now all I have to do, I show up to the call,
it gets recorded, it gets added to our CRM.
I just ping her and I say, Hey, I just finished this call.
They need an analysis. She watches the call, she goes
through, she builds the analysis,
she pings me and it's done.
We jump on a 15 minute call, we review it together,
I jump on the analysis call and I try and close them.
And after that I tell her to put together a proposal,
alert the finance team about sending an invoice,
the onboarding process, all that type of stuff.
So that has really allowed me to say, all right,
let me focus on what I do best,
which is just the selling the analysis part.
The consulting part. Now a prospect,
even the biggest prospects will only take like a maximum two
to three hours of my time over like a couple week process,
uh, period versus 10 to 15 hours.
And when you have multiple deals in the fire, right?
Like we always have at least five deals going on, right?
And we have new leads coming in every week.
So for me to try, like, it was impossible.
And I was trying to do that for a while
after I filed a sales rep
and I was like, I, I can't do this.
Like, it's just too, it's way too much work.
And to me it's such a huge competitive advantage
for us when I have a, a discovery call
and then I have an analysis done
for them in two business days.
It used to take upwards
of two weeks when I was at the previous agency that
that purchased me, they had one full-time
sales rep who was awesome.
He was really, really good at
sales and, and the analysis stuff.
But like, it would take him two weeks to get a proposal done
because he was so backed up.
And by that time, like you wanna talk about
ghosting, they're like, who are you?
And when did we talk? I don't remember talking to you.
You know what I mean? Like, it's too long. Like you
need to get these things done quick.
You need to strike well, the iron's hot while you have
their retention and their interest.
If you have a discovery call
and then give 'em a proposal,
like anything less than three days later, forget about it.
Like it's gone. It's already gone.
So that was probably one of the best hires
that I've made in a very long time.
She's awesome. And also when there's like a not a lot
of deal flow, she helps out with the SEO work.
So she'll jump in and she'll do like, she helps out
with like content outlines a lot
of like on page optimization stuff.
And she's a grinder. She's awesome. She loves to do it too.
So she actually hits me up
and she's like, Hey, I don't have any proposals to do,
like, give me stuff to do.
So, you know, I'm very lucky with her. She's been awesome.
Super helpful. That region
of the world by the way is just amazing.
I mean that we have Elena Dragana,
like we have another person now that works
to highly recommend that region of the world for talent.
It's been, it's been amazing
for us in terms of, in terms of hiring.
So that is what we do.
Are there any specific terms or verbiage
that really resonates to help attorneys close?
Yes. I would say results.
They ultimately want to work with people
that they want to work with.
People that have experience with law firms have results.
And also, like reputable law firms
is a really big thing for them.
So make sure that you're communicating results,
especially ones that resonate
with them from like a practice area point of view.
So that's what I would say,
that's what they care about the most.
If you can get them results, then
they'll, they'll pay whatever it takes.
Appreciate you all. I'll see you inside of Slack. Just.